Guide to the New-York Historical Society Schenectady Collection 1688?-1883, undated (bulk, 1710s-1840s) MS 544
New-York Historical Society
- Field Notes, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  One page of field notes of a Survey along the Mohawk River
- Resolution, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Resolution by the Citizens of the 3rd/4th Ward of the City of Schenectady that Joseph Shuntleff, Esq. will represent the city in the State Legislature
- Petition, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Petition to the Honorable James Delaney from the Inhabitants of the Township of Schenectady to fortify the township
- Page of script, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Scrap of paper with handwriting practice of Mary Empie
- Scrap of paper with handwriting practice, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Note requesting John Empey send Unger Dorkin money
- Letter, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Letter to John Sanders from Arent Vedder regarding cow hides
- Public Notice, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Petition to the State Legislature to authorize commissioners to hear and determine if the said common lands should be divided from the Freeholders and Inhabitants of the Township of Schenectady
- Petition, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Petition to the State Legislature from John Sanders for a toll bridge across the Mohawk River
- Directory of Names, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Directory of names and professions